[{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980342524,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":26073,"timeElapsed":154321},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980356487,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":13961,"timeElapsed":168285},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980367870,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":11380,"timeElapsed":179668},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980382873,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":14999,"timeElapsed":194671},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980390561,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":7685,"timeElapsed":202359},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980393867,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3303,"timeElapsed":205665},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980396737,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2867,"timeElapsed":208534},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980406281,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":9542,"timeElapsed":218079},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980414115,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":7831,"timeElapsed":225912},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980434887,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":19065,"timeElapsed":246685},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980440481,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":5591,"timeElapsed":252279},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980448716,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":8233,"timeElapsed":260514},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980454796,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":6078,"timeElapsed":266594},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980460488,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":5689,"timeElapsed":272285},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980464304,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3815,"timeElapsed":276102},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980467279,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2972,"timeElapsed":279077},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980473593,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":6311,"timeElapsed":285391},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980477562,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":3967,"timeElapsed":289360},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980492909,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":13874,"timeElapsed":304707},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980496725,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":3813,"timeElapsed":308522},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980506975,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":10248,"timeElapsed":318773},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980518764,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":11787,"timeElapsed":330561},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980522385,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":3619,"timeElapsed":334183},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980525029,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2641,"timeElapsed":336826},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980527469,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2438,"timeElapsed":339267},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980532974,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":5504,"timeElapsed":344772},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980535910,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2933,"timeElapsed":347707},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980549226,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":12029,"timeElapsed":361024},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980552248,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3021,"timeElapsed":364046},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980560579,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":8329,"timeElapsed":372377},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980570115,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":9533,"timeElapsed":381913},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980573809,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":3692,"timeElapsed":385607},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980576549,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":2738,"timeElapsed":388347},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980579428,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2877,"timeElapsed":391226},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980583348,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3918,"timeElapsed":395146},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980586809,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3458,"timeElapsed":398606},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980597071,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":9014,"timeElapsed":408868},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980600345,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":3271,"timeElapsed":412143},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980605123,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":4775,"timeElapsed":416920},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980608072,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":2948,"timeElapsed":419870},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980612358,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":4283,"timeElapsed":424156},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980615688,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":3328,"timeElapsed":427486},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980618502,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2811,"timeElapsed":430300},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980623979,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":5475,"timeElapsed":435777},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980627455,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":3474,"timeElapsed":439253},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980637846,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":9249,"timeElapsed":449644},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980647329,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":9480,"timeElapsed":459127},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980655292,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":7961,"timeElapsed":467090},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980660288,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":4994,"timeElapsed":472086},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980664673,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":4382,"timeElapsed":476471},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980667841,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":3166,"timeElapsed":479639},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980670291,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":2448,"timeElapsed":482089},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980674017,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":3724,"timeElapsed":485815},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980679010,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":4991,"timeElapsed":490808},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980680950,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":1938,"timeElapsed":492748},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980690967,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":8819,"timeElapsed":502765},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980695963,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":4994,"timeElapsed":507761},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980700207,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":4242,"timeElapsed":512005},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980703311,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3102,"timeElapsed":515109},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980706165,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2851,"timeElapsed":517963},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980708874,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":2706,"timeElapsed":520671},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980711799,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":2923,"timeElapsed":523597},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980715834,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":4033,"timeElapsed":527632},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980721671,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5834,"timeElapsed":533469},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980726473,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":4799,"timeElapsed":538271},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980738140,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":10177,"timeElapsed":549938},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980740671,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":2530,"timeElapsed":552469},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980744899,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":4226,"timeElapsed":556697},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980747033,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2132,"timeElapsed":558831},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980751108,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":4072,"timeElapsed":562905},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980753816,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":2706,"timeElapsed":565613},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980756346,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2528,"timeElapsed":568144},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980762640,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":6292,"timeElapsed":574438},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980764831,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2188,"timeElapsed":576629},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980774382,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":8313,"timeElapsed":586180},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980778142,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":3757,"timeElapsed":589940},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980781238,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":3094,"timeElapsed":593036},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980784027,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":2786,"timeElapsed":595825},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980786840,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":2811,"timeElapsed":598638},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980789314,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":2471,"timeElapsed":601112},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980794318,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5001,"timeElapsed":606116},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980797833,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":3513,"timeElapsed":609631},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980799757,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":1921,"timeElapsed":611555},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980813828,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":12663,"timeElapsed":625626},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980816446,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":2615,"timeElapsed":628244},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980820746,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4297,"timeElapsed":632544},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980822759,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2010,"timeElapsed":634557},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980827114,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":4353,"timeElapsed":638912},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980830655,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3539,"timeElapsed":642453},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980833088,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":2430,"timeElapsed":644886},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980836353,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3263,"timeElapsed":648151},{"subjectID":"sstl6h09sf","prolificID":"66a90655f7c843384a6c8178","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2525fa784426e024784","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980838236,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1881,"timeElapsed":650034}]